<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Mainly satisfied</title>
  <subtitle>Thoughts about web and life</subtitle>
  <id>http://glenf.github.io</id>
  <link href="http://glenf.github.io"/>
  <link href="http://glenf.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-08-30T03:00:00+03:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>A goodbye</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/a-goodbye/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/a-goodbye/</id>
    <published>2015-08-30T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-30T21:33:03+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">Our oldest dog Iida is 13 years old. She is old for a labrador retriever. And her body is giving up on her. She still has her mind sharp as ever. But her joints are broken. She has been eating pain killers for a couple of years now. When she started eating them she got her spirit and joy back. But recently we’ve started to think if it’s her time to go. The pain killers arenät fixing her. Just easing the pain. So every pain killer I give to her feels like a small goodbye. And it’s hard to say goodbye to someone who’s been in your life for a long time. Even if she is a dog. And especially when you</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Finishing projects</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/finishing-projects/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/finishing-projects/</id>
    <published>2015-08-29T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-30T21:32:56+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">I have hard time to finish my projects. Not the work kind but the hobby and side project kind. I usually start them with enthusiasm but if the project takes a long time or gets lots of interruptions I tend to not finish it. Which is a bad thing. And I&amp;rsquo;ve started to pay attention to it. Which has made me feel guilty. And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really help me finish the project. Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve started to finish my projects. I&amp;rsquo;t might have something to do with the fact that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to feel guilty or bad anymore.  
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>High beams</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/high-beams/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/high-beams/</id>
    <published>2015-08-26T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-30T21:32:46+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">Yesterday I started installing auxiliary high beam lights to my mothers car. She works at night time so the more light the better. She came to our house with the lights and stuff needed for the installation. And I realised that installing aux lights to a newer car isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as install into an 15 years old car. The safety regulations have changed the way bumbers are installed. And there isn&amp;rsquo;t really that much room in the engine bay. I got the install started and wiring mostly done. But I&amp;rsquo;ll have to finish it in another afternoon.
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Old hardware</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/old-hardware/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/old-hardware/</id>
    <published>2015-08-24T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-30T21:32:39+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">This weekend I finally reinstalled a custom ROM to our 2012 Nexus 7. The first Google Tablet. It&amp;rsquo;s not really that old but the mobile operating systems tend to make over two years old hardware obsolete. Apple has made an exception including iPhone 4s in the upcoming iOS 9 update. Also the next OS X still supports my late 2007 24&amp;quot; iMac. Luckily Nexus 7 is easy to modify so there&amp;rsquo;s the possibility to use custom build Android. With this custom ROM, Dirty Unicorns is the name, I managed to get some more life out of our tablet.
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>August</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/august/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/august/</id>
    <published>2015-08-23T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-30T21:32:32+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">I like August. The summer is almost over and fall is coming. It gets dark but it&amp;rsquo;s still warm. You can see the stars without getting cold. It&amp;rsquo;s like everything is preparing for the winter but still enjoying every last warm day the summer has to offer. In a way August is like the place between sleep and awake. It&amp;rsquo;s like the gentle transitionin from state to another. Soon it&amp;rsquo;s fall. It rains, gets dark and cold. It is just miserable before the winter comes. The hard cold transitioning. I do like August. The final lingering kiss of summer. 
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Comic relief</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/comic-relief/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/comic-relief/</id>
    <published>2015-08-22T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-30T21:32:14+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">Well that went as planned. My friday I mean. I left work for a weekend and thought I&amp;rsquo;d fix the carburettor of my lawnmower. I got home and didn&amp;rsquo;t see my kids around. My wife told that we&amp;rsquo;re taking the night off. And we&amp;rsquo;re going to see some stand-up. She&amp;rsquo;d bought the tickets about a month ago. My jaw dropped. She&amp;rsquo;d been keeping that as a secret! For a month! So my work week ended with a lot of laughter. I had a wonderful evening in a good company. I did manage to fix the carb tho.
</summary>
  </entry>
</feed>
