<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Mainly satisfied</title>
  <subtitle>Thoughts about web and life</subtitle>
  <id>http://glenf.github.io</id>
  <link href="http://glenf.github.io"/>
  <link href="http://glenf.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-08-13T03:00:00+03:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>The Flow</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/the-flow/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/the-flow/</id>
    <published>2015-08-13T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-13T15:13:55+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">I&amp;rsquo;m going to take a break after I do this. In a sec. Just a little moment and then I&amp;rsquo;ll go. And that moment stretches to an hour or two. And the posture is all wrong because of all the sitting in the edge of the seat. Spine all twisted. Shoulders collapsed. I know my muscles will ache later but I don&amp;rsquo;t really pay attention to my body. Or outside world. The Flow has me. Code comes easily. Making awesome things. Only thing breaking the Flow is calendar alarm reminding me to pick my kids up after work.
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>School</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/school/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/school/</id>
    <published>2015-08-12T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-12T15:32:29+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">My daughter went to first grade today. This is her first school day. And my first day as a father of a first grader. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure who was more excited, me or her. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to hear what she has to say about the school. Was it fun? Did she get new friends? I&amp;rsquo;m also looking forward to the first parent teacher events. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why because we&amp;rsquo;ve had these in the kindergarten already. Maybe there&amp;rsquo;s something about my girl growing up. Being more independent every day. But still she will be my little girl forever. 
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Test drive</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/test-drive/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/test-drive/</id>
    <published>2015-08-11T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-11T15:40:31+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">Yesterday I had a long test drive with the lawnmover I&amp;rsquo;ve been repairing. When it came to me the gears didn&amp;rsquo;t work and it didn&amp;rsquo;t run that great. A little bit of fixing and a few new parts and it was running. Sort of. I still need to fix the carburettor and the steering but it cuts lawn. And the gears work. It is loud but simple muffler replacement should quiet things down. Considering that this lawnmover is from the 80&amp;rsquo;s it&amp;rsquo;s in a pretty good shape. Whith these fixes maybe another five years more to ride.
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Food</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/food/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/food/</id>
    <published>2015-08-10T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-11T10:16:11+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">On my summer vacation I allowed myself to eat what I like. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get all crazy because I had to consider my kids and wife also. So no &amp;ldquo;icecream all day&amp;rdquo;. I just didn&amp;rsquo;t pay that much attention to what I was eating. Now that I started working again it was time to pay attention to my eating habits and food. Mainly because I don&amp;rsquo;t do my meals at home. I noticed once again that I eat too little. I don&amp;rsquo;t starve but my calorie count should be higher. Again I&amp;rsquo;ll have to learn how to eat enough.
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Routine</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/routine/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/routine/</id>
    <published>2015-08-09T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-11T10:16:11+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">My routine is broken. Not all my routines but my writing one. I started writing things down every day last month. It went fine because every day I had a time when I&amp;rsquo;d write. Usually at morning after breakfast. A few occasions I wrote at the evening before I went to bed but mostly the writing happened in the morning. Until I started my work again. Now after breakfast I leave for work. And at work I&amp;rsquo;ve not had the same kind of routine in writing that I had at home. It seems I&amp;rsquo;ll have to change my routine.  
</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Work</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/work/"/>
    <id>http://glenf.github.io/thoughts/work/</id>
    <published>2015-08-07T03:00:00+03:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-11T10:16:11+03:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tommi Pääkkö</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">I started my work this week. Four weeks of vacation is over. And it&amp;rsquo;s time to do things that I get paid for. Mostly the same things I&amp;rsquo;d do anyways. Writing code, solving problems. I feel I&amp;rsquo;m privileged to work in industry where I can combine one of my hobbies and improve it. As a professional I get paid to solve my clients problems. As a hobbyist I can use cutting edge libraries to do specific stuff. I learn new stuff from my co-workers. And sometimes I can implement stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve fiddled with to a specific client problem. 
</summary>
  </entry>
</feed>
